(Howard:)I'm warning you, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Your threats are empty.
(Sheldon:)Nothing can move me.
- Stop that!
- Get out of my spot!
(Sheldon:)No. That's it.
I am calling campus security.
(Sheldon:)You prepare for the scolding of your life.
(Leonard:)What are you idiots doing?
(Sheldon:)He's trying to kill me, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Video games and rock music
have desensitized him to violence.
(Howard:)Would you please talk some sense
into your lunatic roommate?
(Leonard:)You're both acting like lunatics.
It's just a parking spot.
(Howard:)Not just a parking spot.
(Howard:)He can't handle the fact
that I'm a bigger deal than he is now.
(Sheldon:)Oh, preposterous.
I have been solely responsible...
(Sheldon:)...for this university's
six-Ioop quantum gravity calculations.
(Sheldon:)I have changed the way we think
about Bose-Einstein condensates...
(Sheldon:)...and I am also the one
who got Nutter Butters...
(Sheldon:)...in the cafeteria vending machine.
(Sheldon:)Maybe you missed that news while you were
floating around like a goof in outer space.